let questions = [
  {
  numb: 1,
  question: "Which of the following keywords is used to define a variable in Javascript?",
  answer: "both A and B",
  options: [
    "var",
    "let",
    "both A and B",
    "None of the above "
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 2,
  question: "What keyword is used to check whether a given property is valid or not?",
  answer: "in",
  options: [
    "in",
    "is in",
    "exits",
    "lies"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 3,
  question: "Which of the following CSS style property is used to specify an italic text?",
  answer: "font-style",
  options: [
    "style",
    "font",
    "font-style",
    "@font-face"
  ]
},
  {
    numb: 4,
  question: "Which of the following function defines a linear gradient as a CSS image?",
  answer: "linear-gradient()",
  options: [
    "threw",
    "linear-gradient()",
    "grayscale()",
    "image()",
  ]
},
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What is the use of the <noscript> tag in Javascript?",
    answer: "The Contents Are Displayed By Non JS Browser",
    options: [
      "The Contents Are Displayed By Non JS Browser",
      "Clear All Cokies And Cache",
      "Both A and B",
      "None of The above"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 6,
  question: "Which of the following property is used to align the text in a table?",
  answer: "text-align",
  options: [
    "text-align",
    "align",
    "text",
    "None ",
]
},
{
numb: 7,
question: "Which element is used for or styling HTML5 layout?",
answer: "CSS",
options: [
  "CSS",
  "JQuery",
  "Jvascript",
  "HTML",
]
},
{
numb: 8,
question: "When an operatorâ€™s value is NULL, the typeof returned by the unary operator is:",
answer: "Object",
options: [
  "Boolean",
  "Undefine",
  "Object",
  "Integer"
]
},
{
numb: 9,
question: "Which function is used to serialize an object into a JSON string in Javascript?",
answer: "Stringify()",
options: [
  "Stringify()",
  "parse()",
  "converter()",
  "None"
]
},
{
numb: 10,
question: "Which character is used to represent when a tag is closed in HTML?",
answer: "/",
options: [ 
  "{}",
  "/",
  "$",
  "#"
]
},

];